quikly.com 2017-03-12

# Privacy Policy

_Last Updated: November 2nd, 2015_

**Quikly, Inc. ("Quikly," or "we," or "us") has adopted this Privacy Policy to explain its practices relating to the collection, use,   sharing and storage of data received from or through the use of its website [www.quikly.com](http://www.quikly.com/) (the "Site") and all services offered via the site and all related mobile or online services or applications (collectively "Services"). Unless otherwise defined, any capitalized terms used in this Privacy Policy have the same meaning as in our ** **Terms of Service.**

**List of topics with Links:**

Consent

Collection of Personal Information

Use of Personal Information

Disclosure of Personal Information

Accessing and Updating Personal Information

Collection of Non-Personal Information

Use and Sharing of Non-Personal Information

Cookies and Automatic Information Gathering Technologies

International Users

Children

Information Security

Your California Privacy Rights

Public Message Boards and Other Online Forums

Third-Party Sites

Changes to This Privacy Policy

**Consent**

By using the Site or Services, you acknowledge and agree to this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree with this Privacy Policy, you should not use the Site or Services.

**Collection of Personal Information**

Certain Personal Information (information which can identify you) is required to create and maintain a Quikly user account. This includes your full name, email address, and cell phone number. Quikly or its payment provider may also collect credit, debit or other billing account information. You may choose not to provide certain Personal Information, but this may prevent you from receiving our services.

If you choose to use Quikly’s social networking functions, we may collect your user ID and password information for the social networking site(s) you choose to connect with. We will do so only as necessary to make it easier for you to post to such site(s) or to log in using your social networking credentials from such site(s). By participating in this feature, you understand that you are authorizing us to use any other information, including Personal Information, on your linked social networking accounts. While we do not store social network passwords on our servers, we may store any other social network-related information from the sites that you choose to connect with via our Site or Services. 

Specifically, and without limiting the foregoing, you may use "Facebook Connect" to interact with friends, share on Facebook through your Wall and through friends' News Feeds, and opt or log in to a campaign or account. If you are already logged into Quikly and Facebook, when you click on "Connect with Facebook" you will be prompted to merge your profiles. By proceeding, you are allowing us to access your name, email address, sex, and date of birth, to the extent you have made or make those facts available to Facebook.

You can edit privacy settings or disconnect the Facebook Connect service by visiting the Facebook Application Settings page.

**Use of Personal Information**

We may use your Personal Information in running the Site and Services, including offering you the ability to participate in Quikly campaigns; setting up your account; improving online operations; processing transactions requested by you; sending SMS text messages to your mobile phone to inform you about Quikly campaigns; providing customer service; providing you with newsletters, RSS feeds, and/or other communications or services which you have signed up for or otherwise agreed to receive (for example, messages about special offers); displaying content that is customized to your interests or preferences; sending account- or transaction-related communications such as welcome letters and transaction confirmations; performing research and analysis aimed at improving our products, services and technologies; and managing our systems.

**Disclosure of Personal Information**

Your Personal Information will be shared with the Merchant(s) affiliated with the particular Quikly campaign(s) to which you opt-in to participatefor their own use subject to their own privacy policies. You should review each Merchant’s privacy policy before deciding whether to participate in such Merchant’s campaigns. If you later decide that you do not want that Merchant to use your information any more, you will need to contact the Merchant directly, as we have no control over how Merchants use information after they receive it in a campaign.

We also may disclose Personal Information to companies, agents, contractors, service providers or others engaged to perform functions on our behalf (such as processing of payments, provision of data storage, hosting of our website, marketing of our products and services, conducting audits, and performing web analytics) to deliver Services you request; in such cases, the vendor will only be authorized by us to use your Personal Information to assist us in delivering the Services you have requested, and not for any other purpose.

We also may disclose your Personal Information to third parties when we believe, in good faith and in our sole discretion, that such disclosure is reasonably necessary to:

  * Enforce or apply our Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof;

  * Comply with legal or regulatory requirements or an enforceable governmental request;

  * Protect the rights, property or safety of Quikly, our users or other third parties;

  * Prevent a crime or protect national security; and/or

  * Detect, prevent or otherwise address fraud, security or technical issues.

Please note also that if you choose to use our social networking function to post information to Facebook, Twitter or another social networking site, anyone who has access to your information through that other site will be able to see the information you post there.

Please also note that, if you sign in or link to the Site or Services through any social networking service, such as Facebook, any information you supply (or have supplied) to us becomes subject to the privacy policy of that social network/service. We do not control, and are not responsible for, the privacy practices of such networks or services. You should consult the privacy policy of such networks/services.

We also may share your Personal Information with trusted marketing partners for their own direct marketing to you separately from any Merchant-sponsored Quikly campaign you may opt into.

In the event of a sale, merger, or transfer of all or substantially all of the assets of our company, or in the unlikely event of a bankruptcy, liquidation or receivership of our business, we may transfer our files of Personal Information to any entity acquiring our business.

**Accessing and Updating Personal Information**

You may update, correct, or delete Personal Information manually, in your account preferences, or by contacting us at [hello@quikly.com](mailto:hello@quikly.com). We ask that you identify yourself and the information requested to be accessed, corrected or removed when contacting us regarding your account information. Please be aware that if you delete certain Personal Information, you may not be able to continue to use the Site or Services, and even if you request that we delete your Personal Information, we may need to retain certain Personal Information for archival purposes to satisfy our legal, audit and/or dispute resolution requirements.

If you have any questions, need assistance accessing or changing your Personal Information, or if you would like to have your Personal Information deleted, please email us at [hello@quikly.com](mailto:hello@quikly.com).

**Collection of Non-Personal Information**

Quikly (or third parties that have content embedded on the Site or Services such as a social feature) may also collect from you aggregate, non-individually identifiable or demographic information (“Non-Personal Information”). An example of Non-Personal Information would be system-related information such as IP addresses, use information, browser and browser speed, bandwidth of your Internet connectivity, general location of your device or server and the pages of our Site that were viewed during a visit.

**Use and Sharing of Non-Personal Information**

We use Non-Personal Information for internal purposes to help us diagnose problems, monitor traffic patterns and otherwise continually improve our Services, and we may otherwise use or share Non-Personal Information for any lawful purpose in our sole discretion.

**Cookies and Automatic Information Gathering Technologies**

We use cookies and other technologies, such as pixel tags, web beacons, and clear GIF files, to help manage our online advertising program. These technologies help enable us (or third party advertising services we work with) to learn which advertisements bring users to the Services. They also may enable us (or third-party advertising services we work with) to track the actions of users online over time and across different web sites or platforms to measure statistics of our marketing efforts, and to deliver electronic advertisements that may be more relevant to individual consumers and that will improve the consumer experience. You have the option to select “do not track” settings in your browser. The Site does not currently place ads based on such tracking. Accordingly, the Site does not respond to “do not track” requests at this time. In the event tracking-based ads are placed in the future, we will update this policy to explain how the Site will respond to “do not track” requests. For information about how tracking works for online advertising purposes, and what happens when you elect a do-not-track option, visit [http://www.aboutads.info/choices](http://www.aboutads.info/choices).

**International Users**

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from users residing outside the United States. We do not authorize anyone residing outside of the United States to use Quikly. If we learn that you reside outside the United States, we will deactivate your account and delete all of your account data from our systems. We reserve the right to store data inside or outside the United States, subject to the terms of this Privacy Policy.

**Children**

We do not knowingly collect Personal Information from users under 13 years of age. We do not authorize users under the age of 13 to use Quikly. If we learn that you are a child under the age of 13, we will deactivate your account and delete your data from our systems.

**Information Security**

We utilize reasonable information security measures to safeguard your Personal Information. For example, we utilize Secure Socket Layer (SSL) encryption technology when data is transmitted over the Internet, we have installed firewalls to help prevent external access into our network, and we use password protection and IP recognition for login. Unfortunately, however, no data transmission over the Internet and no method of data storage can be guaranteed to be 100% secure. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your Personal Information, we cannot guarantee its security.

**Your California Privacy Rights**

Under California Civil Code sections 1798.83-1798.84, also known as the "Shine the Light Law," any of our users who are California residents are entitled to request and receive once a year, free of charge, a notice from us describing what categories of personal customer information (if any) we shared with third parties or corporate affiliates for their direct marketing purposes during the preceding calendar year. If applicable, the notice will identify the categories of information shared, the names and addresses of the third parties and affiliates with which information was shared. If you are a California resident and would like to request a copy of this notice, please submit a written request to the following address: 1555 Broadway Street, Detroit, MI 48226\. In your request, please specify that you want a “California Privacy Rights Notice.” Please allow at least thirty days for a response.

Any resident of California who is a minor (under age 18) and who has posted information about him/herself on the Site may request removal of that information from the Site by sending a written request, including specific identification of the information to be removed, to the following address: 1555 Broadway Street, Detroit, MI 48226\. In your request, please specify that you want a “California Eraser Law Removal.” Please allow at least thirty days for a response. Please also understand that removal does not ensure that the posted content or information will be completely or comprehensively deleted, particularly if it has been shared via social media and/or copied by anyone else. 

**Public Message Boards and Other Online Forums**

Please note that when you choose to post messages and/or profile content on messages boards or share via social media and other online forums that we may make available via our Site or Services, such content is viewable by third parties and, in the case of public online forums and your public profile, is publicly viewable. Accordingly, you should exercise discretion with regard to what Personal Information you post via our Site or Services and should not post highly confidential or sensitive information. Quikly is not responsible for how third parties who view your Personal Information may use this information (such as to send you unsolicited messages). Please also remember that we reserve the right to repost, transmit and otherwise use any material you post or share via our Site or Services.

**Third-Party Sites**

Please note that Quikly may provide links to the websites or services of third-party organizations and businesses, as well as the Merchants who offer campaigns via our Site or Services ("Third-Party Sites"). We are not responsible for the privacy policies, practices or the content of websites or services owned by others that you may link to or that may be linked from our Site or Services. Accordingly, we encourage you to review the privacy policies and terms of service of those websites so that you understand how those websites collect, use and share any Personal Information.

**Changes to this Privacy Policy**

Quikly may modify or update this Privacy Policy. You can always check the "Last Updated" date at the top of this document to see when the Privacy Policy was last changed. However, if any material changes are made, Quikly will post a notice of changes to this Privacy Policy on the Site. Your continued use of the Site or Services following the effective date of an updated Privacy Policy constitutes your consent to the contents of such policy. IF YOU DO NOT AGREE TO A CHANGE TO THIS PRIVACY POLICY, YOU SHOULD STOP USING OUR SITE AND SERVICES AFTER THE EFFECTIVE DATE OF SUCH CHANGES, IN WHICH CASE THE PRIOR, UNMODIFIED VERSION OF THE PRIVACY POLICY WILL CONTINUE TO CONTROL YOUR PERSONAL INFORMATION.
